[Music]
Welcome to the
Manulife Vietnam app! To download the app,
please scan the QR code displayed on the
screen or search for Manulife Vietnam on the
App Store or
Shopee to experience the
app's features. To create
your own account, select "Register" on the
login screen
and enter your information as instructed.
[Music]
You will receive an OTB verification code
via SMS. Enter the verification code
and select "Confirm" to complete the
verification process. Then, create a password to
enhance the security of your Manual Life ID account.
Your Manulife ID account
is now successfully registered on the
Manulife Vietnam app.
You can now easily and conveniently manage
your insurance policy information directly on the
Manulife Vietnam app.
Furthermore, you
can log in to the app
faster with facial recognition
or fingerprint recognition. If your mobile device
has this feature,
activate it now for faster logins on
subsequent occasions with Manulife Vietnam.  Getting
insurance contracts and using online services
has never been easier.